Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Articles and Op-Eds, 1956-2013; XVI.
  - Articles, 1956-2017; 1.
    - "Introduction of Chairman F. Eugene Dixon, Jr. and Chancellor James H. McCormick," State System of Higher Education, p.8, November 13, 1997 (Box 982, Folder 28)
    - Published Federalist Society Conference on "Civil Justice and the Litigation Process," Dick Thornburgh Opening remarks, New York Law School Law Review, Vol. XLI, No. 2, p. 537, 1997 (Box 982, Folder 29)
    - "Junk Science-The Lawyer's Ethical Responsibilities," Fordham Urban Law Journal, Vol. XXV, No. 3, Spring, 1998 (Box 982, Folder 30)
    - "Let Starr Do His Job," by Griffin B. Bell, Edwin Meese, III, Richard L. Thornburgh, and William P. Barr, Wall Street Journal Op Ed, March 11, 1998 (Box 982, Folder 31)
    - "The Dangers of Judicial Usurpation of Puerto Rico's Political Self-Determination", Congressional Record, May 7, 1998 (Box 983, Folder 131)
    - "Government Lawyers and Privilege: The Hazards of Wearing Two Hats," On Point, Vol. 2, No.1, p. 11, August, 1998 (Box 982, Folder 32)
    - "A Preview of the Supreme Court's 1998-1999 Term," K&L Appellate Briefs, Vol. 2, No. 9, September, 1998 (Box 982, Folder 33)
    - "Some Reflections on Three Mile Island," No.9 Contemporary Issue Series Occasional Paper, The Clarke Center, Dickinson College, September, 1998 (Box 982, Folder 34)
    - "A Path to Smarter Federal Leadership in Economic Development: Learning, Leveraging and Linking," Economic Development Quarterly-The Journal of American Economic Revitalization, Vol.12, No. 4, November, 1998 (Box 982, Folder 35)
    - Introduction by Dick Thornburgh, The Qui Tam Quagmire: Understanding the Law in and Era of Aggressive Expansion, Washington Legal Foundation, 1998 (Box 982, Folder 36)
    - Defending the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), Supreme Court Amicus Brief filed by Dick Thornburgh on behalf of N.O.D. on the Olmstead Case, March 15, 1999 (Box 982, Folder 37)
    - Ex-Pennsylvania Governor Dick Thornburgh on State's R and D Role, Science and Government Report, Vol. XXIX, No. 9, May 15, 1999 (Box 982, Folder 38)
    - "Dedication to Frank M. Johnson, Jr.," co-authored with Irs Burnim, Mental and Physical Disability Law Reporter, September-October, 1999 (Box 982, Folder 39)
    - "Privileged Talks Boost Compliance," The National Law Journal, p. A29, December 13, 1999 (Box 982, Folder 40)
    - "Attorney-Client Privilege and 'Crime-Fraud' Exception: The Erosion of Business Privacy," Washington Legal Foundation, 1999 (Box 982, Folder 41)
    - "Reflections on the Americans With Disabilities Act," Texas Medical Center News, Vol. 22, No. 5, March 15, 2000 (Box 982, Folder 42)
    - "Judges must bring sanity to punitive damages awards," PMA Legislative Bulletin, No. 27, March 20, 2000 (Box 982, Folder 43)
    - "Supreme Court Preview," by Dick Thornburgh and David R. Fine, K&L Update, Vol. 4, No. 4, July-August, 2000 (Box 982, Folder 44)
    - "Pausing to Reflect on The ADA After 10 Years," by Dick Thornburgh and David R. Fine, Exceptional Parent (EP), Vol. 30, No. 8, August, 2000 (Box 982, Folder 45)
    - "Reflections on the Americans With Disabilities Act," Center News, Houston Law Review, Vol. 37, No.4, Fall, 2000 (Box 982, Folder 46)
    - "Thornburgh Critiques Federal Criminal Code," Ohio Lawyers Weekly, October 2, 2000 (Box 982, Folder 47)
    - "It's Time for a Federal Code," [speech given at 2000 FBA annual convention in Cleveland, Ohio], The Federal Lawyer, Vol. 47, No. 10, p. 45, November/December, 2000 (Box 982, Folder 48)
    - "Tools for Fighting Corruption Worldwide: A Primer," Hearsay, a Deloitte and Touche publication, December, 2000 (Box 982, Folder 49)
    - "The Liability Explosion," Briefly, National Legal Center, Vol. 4, No. 7 (from annual General Counsel Briefing entitled "Corporate Law on the Edge of the Millennium"), 2000 (Box 982, Folder 50)
    - "America's Challenges and Responsibilities in the 21st Century," Vision & Values, Grove City College, Alumni Association Publication, February, 2001 (Box 982, Folder 51)
    - "The McDade Law Creates a Cloud," The Federal Lawyer, March-April, 2001 (Box 982, Folder 52)
    - "ENABLING ACTS" May 25, 2001, by Dick Thornburgh and David R. Fine [and second "Enabling Behavior" May 2001, unknown publication] (Box 982, Folder 53)
    - "Class action retrofit," The National Law Journal/www.NLJ.com, July 16, 2001 (Box 982, Folder 54)
    - "Justice Department Should Study Criminalization of Business Conduct," Washington Legal Foundation "Counsel's Advisory," Vol. 8, No. 13, September 21, 2001 (Box 982, Folder 55)
    - "What Role for the United Nations in Responding to Terrorism," Washington Legal Foundation "Legal Backgrounder," Vol. 16, No. 49, November 6, 2001 (Box 982, Folder 56)
    - Tenth Circuit Judicial Conference re "Growing Federalization of Criminal Law," New Mexico Law Review, Winter, 2001 (Box 982, Folder 57)
    - "Cure for high premiums," The National Law Journal, September 23, 2002 (Box 982, Folder 58)
    - Chapter: "What My Country Means to Me," My America, book edited by Hugh Downs, Fall, 2002 (Box 982, Folder 59)
    - "Junk Science makes junk law," Washington Legal Foundation, February 6, 2003 (Box 982, Folder 60)
    - "Cure for Malpractice Lies With Congress," New York Law Journal, March 17, 2003 (Box 982, Folder 61)
    - "A Recent Supreme Court Punitive Decision Unites Usually-Opposed Justices On the Need for More Guidance in this Area," by Dick Thornburgh and David R. Fine, FindLaw's Legal Commentary, May 28, 2003 (Box 982, Folder 62)
    - "Manage Your CEO--or Else," by Dick Thornburgh and Michael J. Missal, Chief Legal Executive, Vol. 2, No. 3; AND "Youth, Pornography, and the Internet," by Dick Thornburgh and Herbert Lin, Issues in Science and Technology, Fall, 2003 (Box 982, Folder 63)
    - "Fighting Corruption through Multilateral Financial Institutions," Foreign Policy Research Institute, Winter, 2003 (Box 982, Folder 64)
    - "Faith, Ethics and the Law," Princeton Seminary Bulletin, Vol. XXV, No. 1, Spring, 2004 (Box 982, Folder 65)
    - Forward to System under Stress: Homeland Security and American Politics, by Donald F. Kettl, 2004 (Box 982, Folder 66)
    - "Clearing Hurtles," Enabled.com connecting people with disabilities, July 26, 2004 (Box 982, Folder 67)
    - "Dangers of Judicial Usurption of Puerto Rico's Political Self-Determination, April 9, 1998 (Box 983, Folder 131)
    - "The Case for Civil Justice Reform", Georgetown Journal of Law & Public Policy, Volume 2, No. 2, Summer 2004 (Box 983, Folder 132)
    - "Crisis in Corporate Governance? The WorldCom Saga", Executive Counsel, July 2004 (Box 983, Folder 133)
    - "Empowering the 'Good Guys'" (draft), Pennsylvania Lawyer, Vol 26, No.4, July-August 2004 (Box 983, Folder 134)
    - "Diversity and Disability: Recognizing the Talents of People with Disabilities", K&L Gates Issue Paper, Summer/Fall 2004 (Box 983, Folder 135)
    - "Six Lessons from WorldCom" by Thornburgh and Missal, Corporate Counsel, September 2004 (Box 983, Folder 136)
    - "State of Tennessee v. George Lane, Beverly Jones and USA, Respondents, Supreme Court brief No. 02-1667: Dick Thornburgh, NOD, etc. Amici curiae, November 2004 (Box 983, Folder 137)
    - "Balancing Civil Liberties &Homeland Security: Does USA PATRIOT Act Avoid Justice Jackson's 'Suicide Pact'", Albany Review, Vol. 68 No.4, 2005 (Box 983, Folder 138)
    - "Commercial Free Speech", Washington Legal Fdation "Conversations With", Summer 2005 (Box 983, Folder 139)
    - "The Supreme Court - Allow television Coverage", National Law Journal by Thornburgh and D.R.Fine, December 2005 (Box 983, Folder 140)
    - "Organizing a Successful Corporate Internal Investigation", WLF "Legal Backgrounder", April 21, 2006 (Box 983, Folder 141)
    - "Waiver of the Attorney-Client Privilege: A Balanced Approach", WLF "Legal Backgrounder", June 2006 (Box 983, Folder 142)
    - "Foreign Corrupt Practices Act - US legislation with global implications", PLC Cross-border Quarterly, April-June 2006 (Box 983, Folder 143)
    - "Watch Out for Voting Day Bugs", Electronic article with Richard Celeste, August 18, 2006 (Box 983, Folder 144)
    - "Foreign Corrupt Practices Act, Enforcement after US v. Kay", Washington Legal Foundation, 2006 (Box 983, Folder 145)
    - "The Issue: US & International Anti-Corruption Efforts", WLF: "Conversations with…", Winter 2006 (Box 983, Folder 146)
    - "Breaking Down Barriers to Hiring Lawyers with Disabilities", K&L Gates "Diversity" newsletter, Winter/Spring 2007 (Box 983, Folder 147)
    - "Building and retaining trust in biomedical community", Cleveland Clinic Journal of Medicine, March 2007 (Box 983, Folder 148)
    - Keynote speech: "Dedication William R. Eleazer Courtroom", Stetson Law Review, Vol 36, No 3, Spring 2007 (Box 983, Folder 149)
    - "The Dangers of Over-Criminalization & Need for Real Reform: Dilemma of Artificial Entities & Artificial Crimes", American Criminal Law Review, Fall 2007 (Box 983, Folder 150)
    - "Surveillance Sanity", Wall Street Journal, October 31, 2007 (Box 983, Folder 151)
    - "Supreme Court Rejects 'Scheme Liability' Claims by Securities Class Action Plaintiffs", K&L Gates "Stay Informed", January 16, 2008 (Box 983, Folder 152)
    - "Improve Corporate Governance", Brookings Institute "Opportunity '08", March 30, 2008 (Box 983, Folder 153)
    - "Suit to hold manufacturer strictly liable for illegal product use should be dismissed", Washington Legal Foundation "Legal Backgrounder", August 22, 2008 (Box 983, Folder 154)
    - "Maintaining the Corporate Compliance Commitment", Washington Legal Foundation: "Conversation With", Summer 2008 (Box 983, Folder 155)
    - "The Changing Legal Landscape for Intellectual Property", Washington Legal Foundation: "Conversation With", Fall 2008 (Box 983, Folder 156)
    - "Globalizing a Response to Disability Discrimination", Washington Legal Review, Vol. 83 No. 4, November 2008 (Box 983, Folder 157)
    - "The Credit Crisis and Corporate Governance Failures", "Executive Counsel", November/December 2008 (Box 983, Folder 158)
    - Introduction to Special Report: "Federal Erosion of Business Civil Liberties", Washington Legal Foundation Special Report, Second Edition, March 2010 (Box 983, Folder 159)
    - Background Paper re Board Decision Making, National Association of Corporate Directors meeting, March 2, 2010 (Box 983, Folder 160)
    - "US Supreme Court: Mixed Results for the Business Community", K&L Gates: Global Government Solutions, June 2010 (Box 983, Folder 161)
    - "Ruling on Anti-Terror Tactics Subjects Law Enforcement Officials to Personal Liability", Washington Legal Foundation, Legal Opinion Letter: Vol. 18 No 11, June 4, 2010 (Box 983, Folder 162)
    - "WHAT do I know?", Pittsburgh Quarterly, Fall 2010 (Box 983, Folder 163)
    - "Washington Legal Foundation: October 2010 US Supreme Court", Metropolitan Corporate Counsel, Inc., October 4, 2010 (Box 983, Folder 164)
    - "Supreme Court", K&L Gates Global Government Solutions 2011: Annual Outlook, January 2011 (Box 983, Folder 165)
    - "Overcriminalization: Sacrificing the Rule of Law in Pursuit of Justice", Heritage Lectures, March 1, 2011 (Box 983, Folder 166)
    - "Supreme Court Reviewing Cases of Interest to Business", Mainjustice.com, March 9, 2011 (Box 983, Folder 167)
    - "Tribute to NLSA by Dick Thornburgh, Neighborhood Legal Services Association, May 16, 2011 (Box 983, Folder 168)
    - "How to decide who stays in California prisons?", San Diego ONLINE, June 4, 2011 (Box 983, Folder 169)
    - "Foreign Corrupt Practices Act", PLC US Special Report, June 2011 (Box 983, Folder 170)
    - "Deficits Need Balanced Budget Amendment Fix:", Bloomberg, July 20, 2011 (Box 983, Folder 171)
    - "A Balanced Budget Amendment is Not a Nutty Idea", Various newspapers, July 2011 (Box 983, Folder 172)
    - "A Broken Promise Leaves Witness, Family in Danger", USA Today, August 30, 2011 (Box 983, Folder 173)
    - "The Challenge of Over-Criminalization", PA Lawyer Magazine, November-December 2011 (Box 983, Folder 174)
    - "PA High Court May Rule on Minority Shareholders' Rights", WLF Legal Opinion, December 16, 2011 (Box 983, Folder 175)
    - "US Supreme Court's decision: IMS Health Inc. v. Sorrell", WLF Conversations With…, Winter 2012 (Box 983, Folder 176)
    - "Civil Justice Reform in Wisconsin", WLF Conversations With…, Winter 2012 (Box 983, Folder 177)
    - "Competition In Online Search: What Role for Antitrust?", WLF Conversations With …, Winter 2012 (Box 983, Folder 178)
    - "'Equal Justice Under Law': The Role of the Pro Bono Lawyer", PA Lawyer Magazine, January-February 2013 (Box 983, Folder 179)
    - "Shelby County, Alabama v. Eric H. Holder, Jr, Attorney General, et al; Respondents Brief", American Bar Association, February 1, 2013 (Box 983, Folder 180)
    - "Trolling, Licensing & Litigating: A 21st Century Patent Paradigm?", WLF Conversations With…, Spring 2013 (Box 983, Folder 181)
    - New Material Added, December 2014
      Scope and Content Notes
      Additional material in this category was added to the collection in December 2014.
      - "The Role of the Republic of China in Collective Security" ROC Conference publication and full event information, Washington D.C., June 21, 1994 (Box 1039, Folder 1)
      - Amici Curiae, US Court of Appeals, State of Idaho v. F.B.I. Special Agent Lon T. Horiuchi, July 19, 2001 (Box 1039, Folder 2)
      - Considering Employment Law, Civil Rights and Employee Benefits: Report on Supreme Court at Mid-Term (Part 1), K&L Update, March-April 2002 (Box 1039, Folder 3)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations With…Issue: "Asbestos Litigation,", Spring 2003 (Box 1039, Folder 4)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations With…Issue "Consumer Product Regulation," WLF, Summer 2003 (Box 1039, Folder 5)
      - "Living in the Shadows: TMI 25 years later" Patriot News, March 28, 2004 (Box 1039, Folder 6)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations With…Issue "Civil Justice Reform,", Fall 2004 (Box 1039, Folder 7)
      - Washington Legal Founcation: Conversations With…Issue "Rhode Island v. Lead Industries Ass'n, March 2005 (Box 1039, Folder 8)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations With…Issue "Legal Reform in Mississippi,", Spring 2005 (Box 1039, Folder 9)
      - "Thornburgh on Civil Justice Reform," Executive Counsel, March-April 2005 (Box 1039, Folder 10)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations With…Issue: "Legal Reform - A View from the States,", Spring 2005 (Box 1039, Folder 11)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations With…Issue: Commercial Free Speech,", Summer 2005 (Box 1039, Folder 12)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations With…Issue: "International Trade and Non-Tariff Barriers,", Fall 2005 (Box 1039, Folder 13)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations With…Issue: "Prescription Drug Abuse,", Winter 2005 (Box 1039, Folder 14)
      - "What I Believe - 'Without a Reasonable Doubt," Contribution to Larry King Book, "Without a Reasonable Doubt,", November 1, 2006 (Box 1039, Folder 15)
      - Book: "Puerto Rico's Future A Time to Decide," CSIS Press, Washington, D.C. Vol.29 No. 1, 2007 (Box 1039, Folder 16)
      - "Organizing a Successful Corporate Internal Investigation," Washington Legal Foundation, July 2007 (Box 1039, Folder 17)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations With…Issue: "Supreme Court and Jurisprudence & Practice,", Summer 2007 (Box 1039, Folder 18)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations With…Issue: "Benefits of Legal Reform,", Fall 2007 (Box 1039, Folder 19)
      - Biogaphical contribution to novel "Leapholes Afterword," by by James Grippando, 2007 (Box 1039, Folder 20)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations With..Issue: "Free Enterprise - Left Behind after Sarbanes-Oxley?", Spring 2008 (Box 1039, Folder 21)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations With…Issue: "Maintaining the Corporate Compliance Commitment,", Summer 2008 (Box 1039, Folder 22)
      - "DOJ Issues New Guidance That Retreats From Aggressive Pollicies Followed in White Collar Cases," K&L Gates, September 2008 (Box 1039, Folder 23)
      - Brief, Supreme Court, "Ashcroft v. Javaid Iqbal, September 5, 2008 (Box 1039, Folder 24)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations With…Issue; "Overecriminalization and Financial Crisis,", October 27, 2008 (Box 1039, Folder 25)
      - "Waiver of the attorney-client privilege: the need for a legislative solution," Lawyers Journal, November 7, 2008 (Box 1039, Folder 26)
      - "Could Bart Giamatti hve stopped steroids?," Yale Alumni Magazine, February 11, 2009 (Box 1039, Folder 27)
      - Amici Curiae, Supreme Court: "Northwest Austin Municipal Utility District Number One,", March 25, 2009 (Box 1039, Folder 28)
      - Forward to "Caclculus of Character finds a remarkable interplay of social concepts…", By Peter Blanck et al, Cambridge University Press, 2009 (Box 1039, Folder 29)
      - Washington Legal Foundation Legal Opinion Letter, "Ruling on Anti-Terror Tactics Subjects Law Enforcement Officials to Personal Liability,", June 4, 2010 (Box 1039, Folder 29a)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Conversations Wiith…Issue "Threats to Philanthropic Freedom,", Summer 2010 (Box 1039, Folder 30)
      - "What would Atticus Finch do?," National Law Journal, August 11, 2010 (Box 1039, Folder 31)
      - Washington Legal Foundation: Former Attorneys General Urge Dismissal of Case Seeking Damages From Senior Administration Offical: Ashcroft v. Al-Kidd, No. 10-98, August 19, 2010 (Box 1039, Folder 32)
      - Washington Legal Foundation, Conversations With…Issue "Antitrust Law and Policy in the Innovation Age,", September 2010 (Box 1039, Folder 33)
      - "Homeland security, civil liberties and the rule of law," National Law Journal, September 5, 2011 (Box 1039, Folder 34)
      - Brief, Supreme Court, "Clapper v. Amnesty Internatinal" No. 11-1025, August 2, 2012 (Box 1039, Folder 35)
    - New Material Added, May 2017
      Additional material in this category was added to the collection in May 2017.
      - "The Bill of Rights Today," Pittsburgh Tribune Review, July 4, 1997 (Box 1049, Folder 43)
      - "Junk Science - The Lawyer's Ethical Responsibilities" Fordham Urban Law Journal, Vol. XXV, Number 3, 1998 (Box 1049, Folder 44)
      - No. CR-98-30149 United States Court of Appeals for Ninth Circuit: State of Idaho v. FBI Special Agent LON T. HORIUCHI, Defendant - Appellee. Brief of AMICI CURIAE, December 1998 (Box 1049, Folder 45)
      - "The Issue: Punitive Damages" Washington Legal Foundation. Conversations With, Fall 2003 (Box 1049, Folder 46)
      - Nos. 03-334;03-343 Supreme Court of US Shafiq Rasul, et al. v. George W. Bush, et al Brief of Amici Curiae, March 2004 (Box 1049, Folder 47)
      - Nos. 04-1203 NS 04-1236 Supreme Court of US United States of America v. State of Georgia and Tony Goodman v. State of Georgia, et al. Brief of the Honorable Dick Thornburgh and the National Organization on Disability, as AMICI Curiae, August 2005 (Box 1049, Folder 48)
      - No. 05-1401 Supreme Court of US Alberto R. Gonzales, Attorney General v. Victoria Tchoukhrova, et al Brief for the Respondents in Opposition, October 2006 (Box 1049, Folder 49)
      - No. 06-43 Supreme Court of US Stoneridge Investment Partners, LLC, v. Scientific-Atlanta, Inc. and Motorola, Inc. Brief of Merrill Lynch & Co. Inc. as Amicus Curiae in support of Respondents, August 15, 2007 (Box 1049, Folder 50)
      - Legal Backgrounder, WLF, Vol. 23 No 38 "Suit to Hold Manufacturer Strictly Liable for Illegal Product Use Should Be Dismissed' by Hon. Dick Thornburgh and Brendon P. Fowler, August 22, 2008 (Box 1049, Folder 51)
      - No. 07-8521, Supreme Court of US Harbison v. Bell, Warden, Decided April 1, 2009; Amicus Brief for Current and Former Governors Case No. 07-8521 (Box 1049, Folder 52)
      - No. 08-861 Supreme Court of US Free Enterprise Fund and Beckstead and Watts, LLP v. Public Company Accounting Oversight Board and USA as Amici Curiae, August 2009 (Box 1049, Folder 53)
      - No. 08-1555 December 7, 2009 Supreme Court of US Mohamed Ali Samantar v. Bashe Abdi Yousuf et al, Brief of Amici Curiae former Attorneys General... (Box 1049, Folder 54)
      - "Bearing Witness to Chinese Persecution by Dick Thornburgh RealClearPolitics article, December 18, 2009 (Box 1049, Folder 55)
      - No. 10-98 (2) Supreme Court of US John D. Ashcroft v. Abdullah Al-Kidd as Amici Curia, August 18, 2010 and same Nol. 10-98 dated December 20, 2010 (Box 1049, Folder 56)
      - Nos. 11-1057 & 11-1058 US Court of Appeals for Fourth Circuit Commonwealth of Virginia, ex. Rel. Kenneth T. Cuccinelli, II v. Kathleen Sebelius On Appeal Brief of Amici Curiae, 2010 (Box 1049, Folder 57)
      - WLF Litigation updates October 4, 2010 and December 13, 2010…both Commonwealth of Va. V. Sebelius: includes Summary judgement granted for Virginia, October-December 2010 (Box 1049, Folder 58)
      - No. 11-6480 US Court of Appeals for Fourth Circuit Estela Lebron v. Donald Rumsfeld Brief of Amici Curiae, July 18, 2011 (Box 1049, Folder 59)
      - "Laudable goals, Practical hurdles" by Dick Thornburgh Political Essay 2011 American Society of Criminology, Vol. 10 Issue 1 (Box 1049, Folder 60)
      - No. 11-3100 "Oral Argument not yet Scheduled" No. 11-3100 In US Court of Appeals for District of Columbia...United States of America v. Kevin A. Ring, March 2012 (Box 1049, Folder 61)
      - The Issue: Advancing Business Integrity through Corporate Compliance; Conversations With…The Honorable Dick Thornburgh and Larry ThompsonWLF, Spring 2012 (Box 1049, Folder 62)
      - The Issue: WLF Healthcare Information and Commercial Speech after IMS Health Inc. v. Sorrell Conversations With The Honorable Dick Thornburgh Harvey Ashman Paul Clement, Winter 2012 (Box 1049, Folder 63)
      - NY No. 401720/05 Court of Appeals of State of New York People of the state of New York by Andrew M. Cuomo against Maurice R. Greenberg & Howard Smith, September 24, 2012 (Box 1049, Folder 64)
      - NY No. 401720/05 Cuomo against Greenberg & Smith Thornburgh among Amici Curias Correspondence, March 8, 2013 (Box 1049, Folder 65)
      - No. 11-1203 Supreme Court of US Sholom Rubashkin v. USA, Thornburgh among Amici Curiae, April 2010 (Box 1049, Folder 66)
      - PA Bar Association Quarterly January 2012; Notes from University of Pittsburgh nuclear power symposium (Box 1049, Folder 67)
      - Pittsburgh Post-Gazette article re Pittsburgh tech success, interview with Governor Thornburgh, December 28, 2012 (Box 1049, Folder 68)
      - The Rule of Law as Economic Factor, mysl Publishing: Moscow 2013; Thornburgh Chapter 15 "The challenge of overcriminalization" (Box 1049, Folder 69)
      - New York Times media call, March 19, 2013. Topic: Judicial Merit selection (Box 1049, Folder 70)
      - Pittsburgh Tribune-Review interview with Thornburgh, article "Thornburgh: Let Penn DOT run the PA Turnpike, March 31, 2013 (Box 1049, Folder 71)
      - The Issue: WLF Patent Licensing and the U.S. International Trade Commission with Thornburgh, Deanna Tannere Okun and Paul Roeder, Spring 2013 (Box 1049, Folder 72)
      - The Issue: WLF Proposed Amendments to Federal Discovery Rules, with Thornburgh, Rebecca Love Kourlis and John Jablonski, Winter 2014 (Box 1049, Folder 73)
      - Telephone interview by Tribune Review: "Our Greatest Vulnerability", February 14, 2015 (Box 1049, Folder 74)
      - Former U. S. AG: President Trump, please don't cut Legal Services, Fox News, June 15, 2017 (Box 1049, Folder 75)
    - New Material Added, April 2020